thewiseagent.com 2018-06-04

# Wise Agent -Privacy Statement

The Wise Agent LLC (the “ _Company_ ”) respects the individuals who register to use the Services as defined below (the " _Customers_ "), and individuals who register to access the Company’s website. 

This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the site wiseagent.com, or any affiliated site (collectively, the “Site”), use the related applications or services offered by us, or visit any sites that link to this Policy (collectively, the “Services”). This Statement describes our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information. 

Please read this Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, do not use our Site. By accessing or using the Site you agree to this Policy. This Policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check this Policy periodically for updates.

###### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

In connection with accessing our Services, we may collect information which can be used to identify you (the “ _Personal Information_ ”), such as your name, credit card information, shipping/billing address, email address, phone, user name and password, and location. We may also collect information that is about you, but individually does not identify you, or information about your internet connection, equipment you use to access our Site, and Site usage details. 

We collect this Personal Information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us during registration on our Site.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the Site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners. 

###### WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

Any of the Personal Information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

    * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
    * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
    * To improve our Site (we continually strive to improve our Site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
    * To improve customer service (your Personal Information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
    * To process billing transactions. We use a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use billing information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on the Company's behalf.
    * To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Your Personal Information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purposes described herein.

From time to time, we may partner with other companies to jointly offer products or services. If you purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly-offered product or service, we may share the Personal Information collected in connection with your purchase or expression of interest with our joint promotion partner(s). We do not control our business partners' use of the Personal Information we collect, and their use of the Personal Information will be in accordance with their own privacy policies. If you do not wish for your Personal Information to be shared in this manner, you may opt not to purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly offered product or service.

We do not share your Personal Information with business partners unless you specifically opt in to such sharing via an online registration form.

###### HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We have implemented measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All Personal Information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Such information will then be encrypted into our payment gateway provider’s database, which is only accessible by those authorized to access such systems, and who are required to keep the Personal Information confidential. After a transaction, your Personal Information (credit cards, billing address, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

The safety and security of your Personal Information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of Personal Information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information transmitted to our Site. Any transmission of Personal Information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

###### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT THROUGH AUTOMATIC DATA COLLECTION TECHNOLOGIES?

As you navigate through and interact with our Site, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

    * Details of your visit to our Site, including traffic data, location data, other communication data, and the resources that you access and use on the Site.
    * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type. 

We use cookies, which are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser to capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about Site traffic and interaction so that we can offer a more personalized experience in the future.

###### DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personal Information. However, we may disclose aggregate information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

We may disclose Personal Information that we collect or provide as described in this Policy:

    * To our subsidiaries and affiliates. 
    * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business, who agree to keep this Personal Information confidential.
    * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information held by us about our Site users is among the assets transferred.
    * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. 
    * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the Personal Information.
    * With your consent.

We may also disclose your Personal Information:

      * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
      * To enforce or apply our Terms of Use, and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
      * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Wise Agent, our customers, or others. 

All leads generated by our customers and data stored for our customers are held and protected in strict confidence. We do not contact customer leads, nor do we sell to or share customers’ lead information with any other party.

###### HOW CAN YOU ACCESS AND CORRECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

You can review and change your Personal Information by logging into the Site and visiting your account profile page. You may also send us an email at help@wiseagent.com to request access to, correct, or delete any Personal Information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your Personal Information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change Personal Information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the Personal Information to be incorrect.

###### DO WE UTILIZE THIRD PARTY LINKS?

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Site. These third party products or services have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

###### WHAT TYPE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION DOES THE PRIVACY POLICY APPLY TO?

This online Policy applies only to information collected:

      * On this Site.
      * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Site. 
      * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third party sites and services, if those applications or advertisements include links to this Policy. 

This Policy does not apply to Personal Information collected offline.

###### CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

Our Services are intended for and directed towards adults. Our Services are not directed to minors and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from minors. If you are under the age of 18, do not use the Site, make any purchases through the Site, or provide any information on the Site, including your name, email, address, telephone number or address. 

###### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to help@wiseagent.com.

###### TERMS of Service

Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Site at http://www.wiseagent.com/termsofservice.asp.

###### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ Personal Information, we will update this Policy. The date the Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date email address for you and for periodically visiting this Policy to check for any changes. 

###### Contacting US

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.wiseagent.com  
16766 E. Parkview Ave., Suite 201  
Fountain Hills, Arizona 85268  
USA  
support@wiseagent.com  
480-836-0345
